Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
(Driver) Are you Japanese?
Want me to introduce you
to some good-looking babes?
Asshole doesn't even speak English.
(Bellboy) ls. er...
Is this all right. sir?
Thank you. sir.
(Whistles)
(Silent)
Are you going out. sir?
Oh. please don't bother. sir.
You already gave me a tip.
(Bellboy) Please take
the gentleman to this address.
(Driver) Got it.
He worked here a while ago.
but he got into some trouble.
so I fired him.
(Breaking glass)
Damn! Where the fuck
are your eyes. motherfucker?
Huh? What you gonna do
about my wine. motherfucker?
Ain't some old cheap-ass wine.
Gonna cost you $200!
Huh. yeah...huh? Huh?
Shit!
(Groans)
(Phone)
Tobacco.
Hey. who the hell are you?
This is my big brother.
- Hey. whassup?
- Whassup?
(Brother) Where's Denny?
How come he's not here yet?
(Jay) Must be gambling again.
(Brother) Let's go
without him. then.
(Mo) Check it.
(Brother) OK. let's go.
You doing all right?
(lndistinct chatter)
That's how I have
to hit 'em sometimes.
I can feel 'em!
One. two. three. four. let's go!
(Jay) 'You're brothers.
but you don't look alike.'
Yeah. We are half-brothers.
I don't knowthe details.
We were all abandoned.
Isn't that right. my brother?
We were all put in. er.
some funny institution.
My brother paid for me
to come here and study.
And you end up pushing drugs.
Don't say that
in front of my brother.
But he doesn't
understand English anyway.
Is there anything you need. sir?
Do you have water?
I'll get you some right away.
And what time will you be
leaving tomorrow. sir?
Damn! No tip this time!
He gave the maid 100 bucks
to make his bed.
He must be really loaded.
Then the maid left him
$95 change and this note saying.
"You shouldn't spend money
like this. $5 is enough."
If it were me. I'd have kept it.
(Mo) Hell. yeah!
Hey. Denny. What happened?
(Sighs and groans)
Some joker cut me up yesterday. man.
- Who?
- Fuck if I know.
Chink. Some Jap motherfucker. man.
Must've been trying to gank
another tourist.
You don't give up. do you?
Denny. this is my big brother.
He's here from Japan.
Your brother didn't run into me
yesterday. did he?
He's not the one
who fucked my eye up. is he?
What?
All Japanese look the same to you.
You can't tell one from the other.
- Maybe so.
- Well. shall we go?
Yo. Y'all gotta roll without me. man.
man. This shit is hurting.
Then you can hang out
with my brother.
But he doesn't speak English.
What the fuck am I
supposed to do with him?
Drink beer and kill time.
OK. Aniki.
How much beer
are we supposed to drink?
(Silent)
Let's play.
(Traffiic. sirens in distance)
(Denny) 'All right. check it out.'
I'm betting you
six to one odds. all right?
So if I win.
that's six times. all right?
If I bet $10 I get 60 back. OK?
Roll the dice.
Um. ah. let me think...three.
Three. It's gonna be a three.
I know it in my heart.
- Six.
- Oh. you betting. too?
All right. Well. ifyou win
you get $60. you know?.
Let's see who's gonna...
(Chuckling) Ain't that a bitch?
All right.
let's do it one more time.
This time I got two and four
at three to one odds. all right?
So if I get one ofthem.
that's three times. OK?
All right?
Let's see what you got now. player.
Come on. Come on.
What? What?
Six.
No. no! Ain't nobody
gonna get six twice in a row!
You crazy. man. or what?
Well. what is it?
Ain't that a...
Something wrong
with these dice. man!
You're cheating.
Something. God damn!
$20. man...
Hey. where you going. man?
Ah. ta-ba-ko.
Ta..ta-ba-ko. What?
Cigarette.
Oh. tobacco! There's a store
right out there. Check it out.
(Door closes)
Cheatin'-ass mother...
What the hell?
Oh. now. ain't this a bitch?
Oh. yeah.
A fucking hole in the cup?
Son of a bitch!
A hole in the cup!
It's the oldest trick
in the book. man!
I can't believe this shit.
Hand over the money
for the last batch.
All right.
What the fuck is this?
- Fifteen hundred. right?
- No. three Gs.
Hey. that's too much.
That's the price.
We can't make money. then.
Take it or leave it.
I didn't make you sell drugs.
- What are we supposed to do?
- Shut the fuck up!
All right. you cheating son
of a bitch. where's my money?
Mo. get my brother
back to the hotel...please.
- All right.
- Be careful!
What the fuck is going on?
Ken's brother
beat the shit out ofVictor.
(Laughing) That's tight!
Are you the Jap
that beat up the boss. hmm?
Come with us. Come on.
(Mo) Yo. hold up. man.
You don't follow him.
We'll kill you.
Hold up. Then why'd he hit Ken?
(Falls on horn)
(Horn continues)
(Horn stops)
(Car door opening)
(Quiet samba music)
What the fuck do you want.
cabron. huh?
(Speaks Japanese)
Ifyou kill him in one shot.
he'll give you 10 bucks.
My brother says we are
going to war with the cholos.
(Knock at door)
(Jay) What exactly
did he do in Japan?
(Ken) He was a gangster.
(Mo) Who's the other guy?
(Ken) His lieutenant.
(Conversation inaudible)
Where we gonna hide these?
Take 'em out ofthe bag.
- Will it fit?
- Yeah.
Wait a minute.
OK.
So do you think you'd
get away with what you did?
What are you gonna do?
Go to war with us?
We'd wipe you out!
Bring it on. Come on!
(Laughs)
Just relax. We're kidding.
Let's discuss this
like gentlemen. yeah?
We'll give you the territory.
We didn't like those guys anyway.
From now on. you're gonna be
in charge. just as it always was.
You don't have any
objection to that. right?
OK. we accept.
(Door closes)
You told them you'd let them
have the territory.
Why do that for these fucking Japs?
Why not?
We're gonna massacre 'em
all later anyway.
Where did Aniki say we were going?
He said he's meeting some woman.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Hi. guys. I'm Marina.
Nice to meet you.
He's justjoking.
(Ken) 'Hey. where's Denny?'
(Mo) 'lt's his mom's birthday.
he's at home.'
(Ken) 'Doesn't his mom
work any more?'
(Jay) 'She don't need
to be a maid any more.'
(Ken) 'Right. right.'
(Chatter)
- Hey. Thanks for coming by.
- No problem. man. Free food!
Hey. Ma. these are my friends.
- Hello.
- Happy birthday. Mrs Turner.
This is for you. from my brother.
Oh. from your brother? Thank you.
Ah. he's not my brother.
He's not here.
Oh. OK. all right.
Listen. would you guys help
yourselfto cake. please?
OK.
Go on. There's a lot
for everybody. Go on.
(Giggling) Oh. look at this!
This couldn't fit me.
- For Latifah.
- Is it?
- Come on. Come here.
- For me?
Yes. Oh. Latifah.
Oh. my goodness.
You know howto put this on?
That... That...
That bitch took Aniki. took Aniki.
Oh. this is nice.
I knowwhen I'm gonna use this!
Your friends
have such wonderful taste!
There. Let's try this one.
Oh. boy.
OK. OK. how do we get this off?
Ah. here we go.
Ah. this is interesting.
What's in this?
(Woman) Put 'em on!
They knowwhat to get you. don't
they? Don't they? Look at that.
Oh. man.
Now. don't try to be too cool.
Uh-huh.
Come on. relax.
- Ooh.
- Hey. Jay.
I'm Michael Jordan.
- What?
- I'm Michael Jordan.
No. you're more like Michael Gordon.
Not Michael Jordan.
don't get it twisted.
- Michael Gordon. that's you.
- I'm Michael Jordan.
You knowwhat I mean?
Y'all got Michael Jordan?
Not our Michael Jordan.
- I'm Michael Jordan.
- Oh. OK.
- The same Michael Jordan.
- Not the bald-headed Mike.
No. you're like
Shaquille O'Neal right there.
That's who you're like.
- Shaq. you're like Shaq.
- I'm Michael Jordan.
Man. Man.
Er...woman.
Man.
Man. even if
I raise my handicap to 20...
How much more could I win
in an hour? It's crazy.
- Woman.
- Damn.
Woman.
(Chuckling)
The same woman is going
back and forth down the street.
What's going on?
That's Aniki's woman.
(Money counter whirrs)
Ken. would you sign this?
All right.
- Sign. please.
- OK.
You're spending too much.
What are you doing?
Hurry up. do some work!
That was my piece
until a little while ago.
Well. once we take it. it's ours.
Oh. I get it. Kinda like you.
Hey. how's it going?
That ho hasn't called yet. sir.
- How many hos do you have?
- Five. sir.
Business is slow. huh?
Nice fucking shirt!
Japs and niggers! Big fucking deal!
Hey. wanna play some dice?
- Hmm. OK.
- All right. No cheating.
(Laughing) OK.
All right. I'm gonna
call my mother real quick.
(Helicopter overhead)
Hey. what's up. Ma? Yeah. it's me.
I'm gonna be late. all right?
Got some things I gotta do.
Yeah. I love you too. Bye.
Aniki?
(Man) Drop the gun or I'll kill him.
- (Man) Drop the gun!
- Put the fucking gun down!
(Man) I'll kill him!
(Aniki) Shoot! Shoot!
Put the gun down!
(Man) Drop it!
(Aniki) Shoot!
Oh. shit.
Aniki!
He needs rest.
All right.
Sorry. doc. Hope this is OK.
Thanks.
(Gunshots)
Keep your eyes open.
Don't you think it's time
for your brother to move?
He likes it here.
How is he?
Much better.
He was fooling around with Denny.
We caught the pusher who ran away.
What are you doing? Stand up!
Hey! Go to the sushi bar.
Get knife and cutting board.
What are you guys gonna do?
Cut his finger off.
What happens ifyou
cut his finger off?
Erm...he can't
swim straight any more.
How's that?
You can't feel anything. can you?
(Fast. nervous breathing)
Do it.
Do it!
Wait. wait!
I'll give it back. all right?
Just stop the shit.
Don't cut my fucking...
(Screaming) Oh. God!
Get off me!
Oh. shit! You mother-FUCK!
- Hey. Mo.
- Yeah?
Who's the boss of Little Tokyo?
Some. ah. player named Shirase.
- Shirase?
- Shirase.
Should I tell Aniki
ifwe got together.
Iike join up with them.
our family will be bigger?
What do you think?
Joining forces with Shirase
is a bad idea.
- Why?
- He's way too dangerous.
So are we.
Hey. Aniki. want me to
get you some cigarettes?
No. thanks.
- Why?
- My stomach...hurts.
(Sighing) I'm sorry. man.
Justjoking. Joking.
You're messing with me. man.
(Ken) You wait here.
Hey. These fucking guys
want me to be a henchman. you know?.
What should I tell them?
Hey. stop!
(Tyres screech)
The boss says we don't need you.
What is this bullshit? You need me!
You wanna fucking expand.
you need me. I'm the man!
You know how many I killed?
I got a long list of bodies!
Fucking Japs cross me.
you'll be on that long list...
(Gunshot)
You! Come upstairs.
- You did it this time. boy.
- How's your friend feel?
You want some. come and get some
Where you from? (Laughing)
Take care. now.
He's in a bad mood. What happened?
(Groaning)
(Man) 'We got your woman.
'Come to the Sixth Street bridge.
Come alone.'
Shouldn't you take him home?
He doesn't want me to know
where he lives.
(Shirase) Ah...
That's playing it safe. huh?
(Groans)
Isn't Aniki coming?
No. he's got something
to take care of.
Shit!
You know.
he should pay more attention
to the family business.
What shall we do?
It's war.
Fuck with the ltalians.
we'll be asking for trouble.
(Mo) We'll all die.
I'm a Yakuza from the old school.
If I have to die. so be it.
(Man) Freeze!
- Bring him over here.
- Yes. sir.
Who sent you?
Which family?
(Screams)
Aniki?
You OK?
You don't look too good. man.
Gonna eat?
Denny... Run away.
What?
Where to?
Hm. Here. eat it.
Really?
All right.
Hey. boys. Here's to the boss.
Hey. to Don. congratulations.
That's not bad. is it?
(Chatter and laughter)
- Here.
- Thank you.
(Gasping and choking)
(Shirase) We just killed
Geppetti. so it's war.
You better be ready.
The Mafia will torture you to death.
Ifyou get caught.
take one ofthese.
You'll die quickly without pain.
Aniki.
You and l.
we don't need this shit. right?
What a terrible thing to do.
- Clean it up.
- Yes. sir.
(Jay clears throat)
(Explosion)
Aniki.
We are going to avenge
Aniki's death.
Don't even think about running.
(Man) Denny. gimme my 9mm!
OK. buddy. let's go. Colin. Colin!
So. he's dead.
(Shouting and gunfire)
(Heavy gunfire)
(Shouting)
(Screaming and gunfire)
- What is it?
- Some clothes.
Let's go
to my mother's house for now.
OK. Go.
Wait here.
Ma!
(Denny) Oh. God... Oh. God.
Oh. God... Oh. God.
Oh. God. Oh. God. (Sobbing)
Oh. God. Oh. God.
(Door buzzer)
Jay. run!
(Gunshots)
There's only one of 'em.
Let's go.
Aniki. you don't have
to do this. you know?.
This is my business.
Denny. OK. go ahead.
Ahh! Ahh! Oh. God!
(Denny) Oh! Oh. God!
Oh! Oh. God have mercy!
(Denny groaning)
(Guard) Hey. it's all right.
So what do you wanna do with him?
All right. here's how it works.
Now. one ofthese five strings
is attached to the trigger.
You get to choose three.
If none of 'em pull...
we'll let you go. honestly.
All right?
Now go ahead. choose three.
(Denny) Come on.
Come on!
Pick one!
The first one. On the left!
This one? All right.
All right. Choose another one.
Come on!
(Sighing) Ah...fifth one.
Fifth? One. two.
three. four. five...
Pretty lucky guy!
All right. last one.
Come on. come on!
- The second one.
- Second.
God damn son of a bitch!
You motherfuckers!
Get out. Get out!
- Come on. Come on!
- What are you doing?
(Gunshots)
Here. Take it. Run away.
Denny. your eye...
I did it.
Yeah. I know. my brother.
You even killed
one ofyour own men.
You evil son of a bitch. you.
(Phone)
(Ringing continues)
(Ringing stops)
You Japanese are so inscrutable.
(Cars outside)
Run away?
Fucking run away?
Where the fuck am I supposed
to run to. huh? Run where?
These motherfuckers are gonna
kill me no matter where I go.
Fucking shit.
My whole life is fucked up. man!
Just fucked up!
Oh. shit!
I was better off dealing on the
fucking corner. I swear to God.
What the fuck? What am I doing?
And you give me some
fucking stink-ass gym bag
full of stinky-ass clothes. huh?
What the fuck are you telling
me. die in clean underwear?
Huh?
Fucking sick Japanese
tradition or some shit?
Oh. you fucking...
Fuck!
What the fuck
is in this shit. anyway?
Oh. shit.
Holy shit! Holy shit!
Oh. shit!
"Here's the $60
I owe you for cheating.
"plus interest for you.
"Your brother. Yamamoto."
Oh. shit. Oh. shit. man.
Oh. shit. man. Fuck you!
Fuck you. man!
Fuck!
Fucking shit. God damn it!
Oh. shit!
Whoo. Holy shit!
Oh. shit.
Oh. man.
Son of a bitch.
God damn. I love you. man.
I love you. Aniki.wherever you're at. man!
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-